{
    "subject": "resource/Nathaniel_Gorham",
    "predicate": "property/children",
    "object": "Collinsworth Gorham",
    "human_readable": "Nathaniel Gorham has a child named Collinsworth Gorham.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9871416091918945,
            "question": "Is Collinsworth Gorham a son of Nathaniel Gorham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9779292941093445,
            "question": "Is Collinsworth Gorham related to Nathaniel Gorham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9291810989379883,
            "question": "Who are the parents of Collinsworth Gorham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.908839762210846,
            "question": "What is the name of Nathaniel Gorham's child?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8959090709686279,
            "question": "Who is the father of Collinsworth Gorham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.885252058506012,
            "question": "Name one of Nathaniel Gorham's children."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8246665596961975,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Nathaniel Gorham and Collinsworth Gorham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6939896941184998,
            "question": "Does Nathaniel Gorham have any children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6097601652145386,
            "question": "What is the name of Nathaniel Gorham's family member?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5221463441848755,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the family of Nathaniel Gorham?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nathaniel Gorham has a child named Collinsworth Gorham.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1512_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Nathaniel Gorham's family member?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1512_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Nathaniel Gorham have any children?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1512_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Nathaniel Gorham and Collinsworth Gorham?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1512_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1512_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to the text, Nathaniel Gorham married Rebecca Call and they had nine children, including one named Collinsworth."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context mentions that Nathaniel Gorham had nine children, including one named Collinsworth. Therefore, the information supports the statement that Nathaniel Gorham has a child named Collinsworth Gorham."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}